SpaceX is absolutely ripping tonight
as investors continue to pile into this new IPO.
There's so much hype around this.
We don't know if this is the bubble
or if this is a legit valuation.
We're approaching $3 trillion on this company now.
We're starting to see a little bit of a rotation
out of Tesla.
It's down a couple of percent overnight.
And as we can see,
the money is just continually flowing into SpaceX.
The FOMO is real.
The hype is real.
Now we got to know and see if this company
can build into its valuation.
I'd be careful here.
I would not deploy too much money at these levels.
Let it come down.
This is looking like a meme stock at the moment,
but this was anticipated.